You
The creation of a top folder is the first step to connect linka with an issue.
Click the right mouse button that is object and select the top folder.
Import a software linka, point the folder and click on the right mouse button to choose.
Add this new project and then follow the instruction to associate a dual index file.
Now the user has to create our workspace.
Point mouse on the created folder, click the right mouse button and choose our workspace.
Double click to activate it.
In the same way, we can add those on experiment and associate experiment and project.
Select the bottom folder experimental project to import or export from database object and then click with the right mouse button.
And select the import or export.
The first step is the selection of the source.
The user has to choose also the comparing data set, click with the right mouse button in comparing destination and select a data set or from file.
We can choose in action the operation, compare copy or list and format to save the comparison data.
You can start to compare in HTML format, click with the right mouse button and select add or add only.
We can select equal or different to see equal or different variables between the two data set.
Now we can choose the destination folder.
Now we can analyze the comparison file in HTML format.
Finally, allows the post-processing analysis the user can check the variable acquired in Inca.
Open the program and choose new configuration and then click add to choose the file acquired in Inca in that format.
The user can choose the variable to display in variable explorer and the display mode.
Drag and drop the shield scope and then the variable or calibration to analyze.
To display the selected variables more clearly, the user can elite them and click the right mouse button and choose move to individual strip and then zoom to fit.
Now click show icon to analyze the log.
Now we can see the signal values and the difference between two points.